

1 +94 76 603 9161

fb.me/cruz404

ABOUT ME

I achieved all Island first place in A\L Examination 2015 in Engineering Technology stream with the highest Z-Score of 3.4869. Then I completed my Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology (BICT) Honours Degree with Second Class Upper Division (3.46 GPA, 4 Years, 120 Credits) at the Faculty of Technology, USJ. Currently, I work as a Freelancer Fullstack Web Developer for an US-based Company. Also I work as a Visiting Lecturer at SLIIT, Kandy Campus. I am interested in completing postgraduate studies and entering the field of academics. I am enthusiastic about what I do and always looking to improve my skills.

SKILLS & GOALS

IT skills

Front End Web development (Angular) Backend Web Development (Django, Laravel, Slim) Database (MySQL, Sqlite, Firebase) Hybrid Mobile App Development (Flutter, Ionic3) Desktop Application Development (Python + QT) Chat Bot Development (RASA) Web Scraping and Automations with Python Image Processing (Python + OpenCV)

Leadership skills

Former President - USJ FOSS Community Founder Member - J'pura TechTalks Founder Member - CodeChamps Online Hackathon President - ICT Societ of St. Thomas College (2014-2015) Secretary - Media Unit St. Thomas College (2014-2015)

Goals

Start and Complete PhD in next 10 years

PROFESIONAL SKILLS

PYTHON		
JAVASCRIPT		
ANGULAR		
PHP		
MYSQL		

PERSONAL DETAILS

Samarakoon Mudiyansela Adikaramlage Full Name

Walawwe Shanaka Anuradha Samarakoon

Name with Initials S.M.A.W.S.A.Samarakoon

Address Infront Of School, Maningamuwa,

Pallepola, Matale.

Date of Birth 24-03-1995

Gender Male Marital Status Single Nationality Sri Lankan Nic No. 950840080v

EDUCATION

GCE Ordinary Level Examination / 201

St. Thomas College Matale

Sinhala Α Buddhism Mathematics Α Science Α English Α Citizen Studies Α History Α В Information and Communication Technology Sinhala Literature C

GCE Advanced Level Examination / 2015

St.Thomas College Matale

	Engineering Technology	Α
Science For Technology		А
Information and Communication Technology		/ A
	General English	В
	District Rank	01
	Island Rank	01
	Z-Score	3.4869

Bachelor of Information and Communication Technology (Honours) - Second Class Upper

Faculty of Technology

University of Sri Jayewadenepura

Bachelor's degree in Information and Communication Technology at the Faculty of Technology, University of Sri Jayewardenepura, Gangodavila, Nugegoda.

GPA - 3.46 / 4.0



+94 76 603 9161

shanaka.vitaz.de

in bit.ly/shanaka95

shanaka95@gmail.com

github.com/shanaka95

fb.me/cruz404

hanakas3 🕕 hackerrank.com/shanaka95

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Trainee Software Engineer - CodeGen Intl (Pvt) Ltd

Kriyo Project | May 2020 to September 2020

Top Rated Fullstack Developer - Upwork

Web Developer at AbrioCare 2020 Nov - Present More than 10 Successfull Projects

Lecturer - Fulltime

Faculty of Computing - Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology, Kandy Center Feb 2022 - June 2022

Lecturer - Visiting

Faculty of Computing - Sri Lanka Institute of Information Technology, Kandy Center
July 2022 - Present

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

All Island First Place - GCE A/L Examination

Engineering Technology Stream Z-Score - 3.4869

Student of the Year 2015

Achieved "Student of the Year" award for year 2015 in St.Thomas College Matale.

Sakura Science Program 2016

Represented SriLanka Team in Sakura Science Program 2016 in Japan, Oraganized by Ministry of Education, Japan.

Codefest 2018 - Merit Place

Won Merit place in Codefest 2018 in "Hackme if you can" CTF Organized by SLIIT.

CloudHack 2017 UCSC - 4th place

OUSL Impacto 2017 - 4th Place

4th place in OUSL impacto 2017 robotic Competition organized by Open University Sri Lanka.

• iHack 2017 Hackathon

Participated in iHack 2017 hackathon organized by UCSC and won the "most popular team" title.

PARTICIPATIONS

Infotel 2018 Innovation Pavilion

Participated in Infotel 2018 innovation pavilion. (EyeRescue project).

HackX 2018 Hackathon

Participated in HackX 2018 hackathon organized by University of Kelaniya.

RealHack Hackathon 2018

Participated in RealHack Hackathon 2018 Organized by University of Kelaniya.

Participated in IESL TechnoHack 2017

CyberFest 2018 CTF Hackathon

Participated in CyberFest 2018 CTF Hackathon organized by NIBM.

Mobitel NB-IoT 2018 Hackathon

Participated in Mobitel NB-IoT 2018 hackathon.

iFest Conference

Participated in iFest Conference organized by UCSC.

Mozilla Global Sprint 2018

Participated in Mozilla Global Sprint 2018 organized by WSO2.

Participated in Cyber Security Summit 2018

Participated in CERT CSW Quiz 2019

RoboFest 2018

Participated in Robofest 2018 organized by SLIIT

CodeFest 2019

Participated in Codefest 2019 in "Hack me if you can" CTF organized by SLIIT

Exhibitions at leading Public Schools

Participated in ICT related Exhibitions as a member of Faculty of Technology Team.

"Boost Your business with Facebook" Workshop

Participated in "Boost Your business with Facebook" workshop organized by Facebook.

PAGE 02 OF 03



- +94 76 603 9161
- shanaka.vitaz.dev
- in bit.ly/shanaka95
- shanaka95@gmail.com
- github.com/shanaka95
- fb.me/cruz404
- upwork.com/fl/shanakas3 (H) hackerrank.com/shanaka95

VOLUNTEERING

DevFest 2019 (GDG SriLanka)

Volunteered in DevFest SriLanka 2019 as a Technical Volunteer - PhotoBooth Application

Disrupt Asia 2019

Volunteered in Disrupt Asia 2019

NON-RELATED REFEREES

Dr. Senaka Amarakeerthi

B.Sc Hons (SUSL, Sri Lanka), MSc (PDN, Sri Lanka), PhD (Aizu, Japan) Senior Lecturer (Grade I), University of Sri Jayewardenepura, +9471 204 3212 senaka@sjp.ac.lk

Dr. Nimal Skandhakumar

B.Sc Eng. (Hons) (Moratuwa), PhD in Information Security (QUT), Senior Lecturer in Computer Science, University of Sri Jayewardenepura, +9476 980 4524 nimal@sjp.ac.lk

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Undergraduate Thesis

Generate multi-instrumental progressions for given melodies using Generative Adversarial Networks(GAN)

Conference Papers

Bypassing Content-based internet packages with an SSL/TLS Tunnel, SNI Spoofing, and DNS spoofing (Pending publication)

RESEARCH INTERESTS

- + Cloud Computing
- + Blockchain Technology & Cryptocurrencies
- + Cyber Security
- + Image Processing
- + Industrial Automations

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- + Blogging
- + Volunteering
- + Cryptocurrency Investments
- + Computer Games

CONSENT

I hereby declare that all above-mentioned information is in accordance with fact or truth up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibilities for the correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

